Guide to the David Trinidad Papers ca. 1970-2002 MSS.106
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Correspondence
  - Subseries A: General Correspondence 1970-1998
    - COOPER, DENNIS. 2 copies of My Mark manuscript., undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - COOPER, DENNIS. works. copy of "A Herd" manuscript., undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - COOPER, DENNIS. 1981 birthday poem to DT (in black folder with skull): Ghost Stories (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - COOPER, DENNIS. inscribed copies of Tiger Beat, Antoine Monnier, The Missing Men, My Mark, and He Cried., undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - COOPER, DENNIS. copy of Coming Attractions inscribed by 16 of the 22 contributors; etc., undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - CORBER, MITCH. 2 letters, 1 postcard; ca. 1996-1997; plus Thin Air Video catalogue with video featuring DT. (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - CORBETT, WILLIAM. 5 letters, 3 postcards; dated 1995-1998. (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - CORY, JIM. 20 letters, 7 postcards, 2 cards, 1 email; dated 1990-1998; plus 12 pages of poetry. (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - COVINO, PETER. 1 letter; dated 1995. (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - CRASE, DOUGLAS. 3 letters; dated 1988-1996. (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - CROSBIE, LYNN. 19 letters, 5 postcards, 4 faxes, 2 emails; dated 1993-1998; plus 2 pages of poetry. (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - CROWLEY, MART. 5 letters, 1 postcard; dated 1998. (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - CUSHING, JIMM. 1 letter; dated 1998. (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - DALY, MEG. 4 letters, 4 emails; dated 1992-1998; plus 5 pages of poetry. (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - DAVIDSON-CAPAZ, LANCE M. 3 emails; dated 1998. (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - DEANOVICH, CONNIE. 40 letters, 22 postcards, 4 cards; dated 1985-1998; plus 2 pages of poetry. (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - DES MARAIS, ELISABETH. 7 letters, 2 postcards; dated 1980-1987. (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - DEVEREAUX, JEAN (childhood neighbor). 4 letters, 1 card; dated 1988-1992. (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - DIDION, JOAN. 1 letter; dated 1997. (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - DIECKMANN, KATHERINE. 1 letter, 1 postcard; dated 1995-1996. (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - DILLARD, GAVIN GEOFFREY. 3 letters, 2 emails; dated 1997-1998; plus page proofs for A Day for a Lay anthology. (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - DLUGOS, TIM. 21 letters, 9 postcards, 2 cards; dated 1981-1990; plus numerous pages of poetry, fliers, reviews, etc.; copy of Folly in the Sahara (#10 of 10 copies privately printed in 1975). (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - DLUGOS, TIM. inscribed copies of High There, For Years, Je Suis Ein Americano, A Fast Life, Entre Nous, and Strong Place (privately printed edition); etc., undated (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - DLUGOS, TIM. copy of Powerless manuscript, undated (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - DLUGOS, TIM. copy of A Fast Life manuscript, undated (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - DLUGOS, TIM. misc. poems., undated (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - DLUGOS, TIM. reviews/readings of Powerless, undated (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - DORLAND, ELLEN B. 2 letters; dated 1979. (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - DORLAND MOUNTAIN COLONY. 3 letters; dated 1979-1986; plus 1986 open house brochure. (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - DORN, TERRY. 1 letter; dated 1981. (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - DOWLING, JACK. 4 letters; dated 1995-1996. (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - DUHAMEL, DENISE. 2 letters, 2 postcards; dated 1994-1998. (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - EBERSOLE, LUCINDA. 5 letters; dated 1992-1994. (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - ELLEDGE, JIM. 15 letters, 23 emails; dated 1992-1998; plus galleys of Essay with Movable Parts corrected by DT. (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - ELMSLIE, KENWARD. 2 postcards; ca. 1981-1985. (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - ENZI, CHRISTOPHER (Christopher N.). 1 letter; dated 1990. (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - EPPERSON, JOHN (Lypsinka). 1 postcard; dated 1997. (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - EQUI, ELAINE. 28 letters, 21 postcards, 11 cards; dated 1980-1997; plus 34 pages of poetry; 4 letters by Jerome Sala (2 of which are joint letters with EE); inscribed copies of Federal Woman and Rose of Lima [removed to Downtown]. (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - EQUI, ELAINE. Nothing Personal essay; and inscribed galley of Surface Tension., undated (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - FARANOVICH, RON. 4 letters, 1 postcard, 2 emails; dated 1986-1998. (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - FERGUSON, SCOTT. 2 letters; dated 1990-1998. (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - FERLINGHETTI, LAWRENCE. 1 letter; dated 1990. (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - FIELD, EDWARD. 4 letters, 3 postcards; dated 1985-1996. (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - FISHER, JOCELYN. 1 letter; dated 1981. (Box 2, Folder 78a)
    - FLANAGAN, BOB. Inscribed copies of The Wedding of Everything, Slave Sonnets; plus lettered copy (D) of Slave Sonnets signed by BF and Mike Kelley., undated (Box 2, Folder 78b)
    - FLANAGAN, TIM. 1 letter; ca. 1985 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - FOURCADE, DOMINIQUE. 1 letter; ca. 1985 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - FOYE, RAYMOND. 16 letters, 9 postcards; dated 1985-1993; plus galleys of November and Three Stories corrected by DT. (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - FRANK, TOM. 4 letters; dated 1994-1996. (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - FRIEDMAN, MICHAEL. 12 letters, 3 postcards; dated 1985-1997; plus 5 pages of poetry. (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - FRIES, KENNY. 2 letters; dated 1990-1991. (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - GAGE, DIANE. 1 letter; dated 1981. (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - GAITSKILL, MARY. 1 letter; dated 1990. (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - GALASSI, JONATHAN. 6 letters; dated 1985-1987. (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - GALVIN, SALLY (maiden name: Eppling). 3 emails; dated 1998. (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - GARRETSON, PETER J., JR. 1 letter; ca. 1976 (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - GARRETT, ALEXANDRA. 1 letter; dated 1988. (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - GERSTLER, AMY. 39 letters, 26 postcards, 5 cards, 21 faxes, 22 emails; dated 1980-1998; plus numerous pages of poetry; inscribed copies of Yonder, Christy's Alpine Inn; inscribed copies of White Marriage & Recovery, and Martine's Mouth [removed to Downtown] (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - GERSTLER, AMY. cont'd, undated (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - GERSTLER, AMY. various fliers and announcements., undated (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - GERSTLER, AMY. MS. of Early Heaven., undated (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - GERSTLER, AMY. MS. of The True Bride., undated (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - GERSTLER, AMY. MS. of Bitter Angel., undated (Box 2, Folder 96)
    - GERSTLER, AMY. MS. of Nerve Storm., undated (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - GERSTLER, AMY. MS. of Crown of Weeds., undated (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - GERSTLER, AMY. "Medieval Torture" broadside, undated (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - GERSTLER, AMY. work., undated (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - GERSTLER, AMY. inscribed galleys of Bitter Angel and Nerve Storm; etc., undated (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - GIBSON, SCOTT A. 2 letters; dated 1998. (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - GILGUN, JOHN. 1 letter; dated 1991. (Box 2, Folder 103)
    - GILSDORF, ETHAN. 2 letters; dated 1991. (Box 2, Folder 104)
    - GINSBERG, ALLEN. 1 letter; dated 1996; plus handwritten copy of "After Class"; and inscribed copy of Your Reason & Blake's System. (Box 2, Folder 105)
    - GIZZI, PETER. 1 letter; dated 1994. (Box 2, Folder 106)
    - GLUCK, ROBERT. 1 letter; dated 1997. (Box 2, Folder 107)
    - GOLDIN, NAN. 1 postcard; dated 1991. (Box 2, Folder 108)
    - GOOCH, BRAD. 1 postcard; dated 1985. (Box 2, Folder 109)
    - GRADY, PAUL. 1 letter; dated 1986. (Box 2, Folder 110)
    - GRAPES, JACK. 1 postcard; dated 1985. (Box 2, Folder 111)
    - GRAY, JANET. 14 letters, 2 postcards, 7 emails; dated 1987-1998; plus 14 pages of poetry. (Box 2, Folder 112)
    - GROSSMAN, RICHARD. 1 letter; dated 1997. (Box 2, Folder 113)
    - GUEST, BARBARA. 2 letters; dated 1989. (Box 2, Folder 114)
    - GUNN, THOM. 1 postcard; dated 1990. (Box 2, Folder 115)
    - H (last name unknown), ADAM (Claude Peck's boyfriend). 1 letter; dated 1989. (Box 2, Folder 116)
    - HACKER, MARILYN. 1 letter; ca. 1994 (Box 2, Folder 117)
    - HAGEDORN, JESSICA. 1 postcard; dated 1998. (Box 2, Folder 116)
    - HAINLEY, BRUCE. 7 letters, 2 postcards; dated 1991-1998. (Box 2, Folder 119)
    - HALL, CHANEY. 1 letter; dated 1989. (Box 2, Folder 120)
    - HALL, STEVEN. 5 letters, 3 postcards; ca. 1984-1988; plus 2 pages of poetry. (Box 2, Folder 121)
    - HARRIS, JANA. 11 letters, 4 postcards, 2 cards; dated 1982-1994; plus 5 pages of poetry. (Box 2, Folder 122)
    - HARRIS, JAYNE ANNE. 1 letter; dated 1994. (Box 2, Folder 123)
    - HARRIS, MARIE. 2 letters; dated 1987. (Box 2, Folder 124)
    - HARRITY, CHRISTOPHER. 12 letters, 3 postcards, 3 cards; dated 1984-1990 plus 2 letters from CH's mother to DT, dated 1985-1990. (Box 2, Folder 125)
    - HARY, LAUREEN (married name: Burger). 40 letters, 7 postcards, 3 cards dated 1970-1984. (Box 2, Folder 126)
    - HASS, ROBERT. 1 postcard; dated 1998. (Box 2, Folder 127)
    - HEALY, ELOISE KLEIN. 9 letters, 2 postcards, 1 card; 1981-1998; plus 4 pages of poetry. (Box 2, Folder 128)
    - HEIM, SCOTT. 6 letters, 3 postcards; dated 1991-1994; plus 5 pages of poetry. (Box 2, Folder 129)
    - HELLER, KATHY. 2 letters, 1 card; ca. 1979-1981; plus 1 page of poetry. (Box 2, Folder 130)
    - HEMPEL, WES. 4 letters; dated 1985-1992; plus 2 pages of poetry. (Box 2, Folder 131)
    - HENRY, GERRIT. 1 letter; dated 1992; plus 1 page of poetry. (Box 2, Folder 132)
    - HEWITT, CHRISTOPHER. 1 letter; dated 1992. (Box 2, Folder 133)
    - HEYMAN, MARK. 2 letters; dated 1977-1979. (Box 2, Folder 134)
    - HICKMAN, LELAND. 13 letters; dated 1979-1981. (Box 2, Folder 135)
    - HIRSHFIELD, DEBORAH. 3 letters, 1 postcard, 3 emails; dated 1993-1997; plus print out of "David's World" web site; and CD Rom of DT's poems. (Box 3, Folder 136)
    - HOLLAND, WALTER R. 1 letter; dated 1998; plus copy of "The Calamus Root: A Study of American Gay Poetry Since World War II," in which DT is mentioned. (Box 3, Folder 137)
    - HOLMAN, BOB. 1 letter; dated 1985. (Box 3, Folder 138)
    - HOOVER, PAUL. 5 letters; dated 1985-1998. (Box 3, Folder 139)
    - HORNER, BRITT. 1 letter; dated 1985. (Box 3, Folder 140)
    - HOWARD, RICHARD. 2 letters; ca. 1993-1994. (Box 3, Folder 141)
    - INDIGO. 1 letter; dated 1994. (Box 3, Folder 142)
    - ISERMANN, JIM. 19 articles and show announcements; ca. 1981-1994. (Box 3, Folder 143)
    - ISON, JOHN. 1 letter; dated 1992. (Box 3, Folder 144)
    - JAFFE, RONA. 1 letter; dated 1997. (Box 3, Folder 145)
    - JIMENEZ, VITA. 2 letters; dated 1991-1997. (Box 3, Folder 146)
    - JONES, PATRICIA SPEARS. 2 letters, 1 postcard; dated 1998; plus 16 pages of poetry. (Box 3, Folder 147)
    - JOSEPH, LAWRENCE. 2 letters, 1 card; dated 1994-1997. (Box 3, Folder 148)
    - JURKIEWICZ, LESZEK. 8 letters, 3 postcards, 5 cards; dated 1987-1992. (Box 3, Folder 149)
    - KAMPER, IRIS. 1 letter; dated 1974. (Box 3, Folder 150)
    - KAPELOS, GEORGE THOMAS. 1 letter; dated 1991. (Box 3, Folder 151)
    - KAPLAN, ROBERT. 1 letter; dated 1986. (Box 3, Folder 152)
    - KARR, MARY. 1 letter; dated 1997. (Box 3, Folder 153)
    - KASZYNSKI, GAIL. 9 letters, 1 postcard; dated 1983-1986. (Box 3, Folder 154)
    - KATZ, ELIOT. 1 letter; dated 1995; plus French translation of "Driving Back from New Haven"; and permission letter for French anthology. (Box 3, Folder 155)
    - KATZ, VINCENT. 2 letters; dated 1996. (Box 3, Folder 156)
    - KAUFMAN, ALAN. 2 letters, 8 emails; dated 1998. (Box 3, Folder 157)
    - KENNEDY, JEFFERY. 2 letters; dated 1990. (Box 3, Folder 158)
    - KERNAN, NATHAN. 1 letter, 1 postcard; dated 1997. (Box 3, Folder 159)
    - KIKEL, RUDY. 1 letter; dated 1985. (Box 3, Folder 160)
    - KILLIAN, KEVIN. 25 letters, 2 cards, 3 emails; dated 1985-1998; plus 3 pages of poetry; 11 pages of reviews; and 9 pages of galleys. (Box 3, Folder 161)
    - KIMBALL, JACK. 1 letter, 2 emails; dated 1998. (Box 3, Folder 162)
    - KLEIN, MICHAEL. 2 letters; dated 1988. (Box 3, Folder 163)
    - KLIMENTOVA, EVA (Revolver Revue). 2 letters; dated 1995-1996. (Box 3, Folder 164)
    - KNECHTEL, TOM. 1 card; dated 1998. (Box 3, Folder 165)
    - KOBOSA, DAVID. 38 letters, 1 postcard, 6 cards; dated 1972-1998. (Box 3, Folder 166)
    - KOERTGE, RON. 2 postcards; dated 1985-1991. (Box 3, Folder 167)
    - KOESTENBAUM, WAYNE. 8 letters, 6 postcards; dated 1990-1998. (Box 3, Folder 168)
    - KOHN, VICTORIA. 2 letters, 6 postcards; dated 1994-1998. (Box 3, Folder 169)
    - KOO, CAROLYN. 6 letters; dated 1992-1995. (Box 3, Folder 170)
    - KRALICK, JOHN E. 35 letters, 30 postcards, 27 cards; dated 1973-1998. (Box 3, Folder 171)
    - KRALICK, JOHN E. cont'd, undated (Box 3, Folder 172)
    - KRALICK, JOHN E. numerous copies of early poems by DT in JK's possession., undated (Box 3, Folder 173)
    - KRUKOWSKI, DAMON. 4 letters; dated 1993-1996; plus 22 pages of poetry; and 4 music related items. (Box 3, Folder 174)
    - KRUSOE, JAMES. 16 letters; ca. 1981-1994; plus 3 pages of poetry. (Box 3, Folder 175)
    - KUSKULIS, VALERIE (friend of Rachel Sherwood). 2 letters; ca. 1990 (Box 3, Folder 176)
    - KUZMA, GREG. 1 letter; dated 1981. (Box 3, Folder 177)
    - LA BOMBARD, JOAN. 1 letter, 3 postcards; dated 1988. (Box 3, Folder 178)
    - LALLY, MICHAEL. 4 letters, 1 postcard; dated 1981-1987. (Box 3, Folder 179)
    - LANDAU, COOKIE. 3 letters, 1 postcard; ca. 1993 (Box 3, Folder 180)
    - LARKIN, JOAN. 3 letters, 3 email; dated 1994-1998. (Box 3, Folder 181)
    - LASSELL, MICHAEL. 4 letters, 3 cards, 1 email; dated 1991-1998; plus 8 pages of poetry. (Box 3, Folder 182)
    - LAUTERBACH, ANN. 1 letter; dated 1996. (Box 3, Folder 183)
    - LEE, MICHELE. 1 inscribed invitation; dated 1998. (Box 3, Folder 184)
    - LEHMAN, DAVID. 5 letters, 3 postcards; dated 1991-1998. (Box 3, Folder 185)
    - LEVY, RONNA. 5 letters, 1 card; dated 1989-1998. (Box 3, Folder 186)
    - LINDSAY-JEWETT, KATHE. Memorial biography; dated 1987. (Box 3, Folder 187)
    - LONG, ROBERT. 1 letter; dated 1993. (Box 3, Folder 188)
    - LORD, M. G. 1 letter, 1 postcard; dated 1995. (Box 3, Folder 189)
    - LUKE, GARY. 3 letters; dated 1992-1993. (Box 3, Folder 190)
    - LYONS, KIMBERLY. 1 letter; dated 1998; plus 5 pages of poetry; inscribed copy of Oxygen; and 18-page Xerox of In Padua., 199818- (Box 3, Folder 191)
    - MAC DONALD, LAURA. 3 letters, 3 postcards; dated 1994-1996. (Box 3, Folder 192)
    - MC CAIN, GILLIAN. 4 letters, 1 postcard; ca. 1995-1998; plus 9 pages of poetry. (Box 3, Folder 193)
    - MC CORMACK, DEREK. 7 letters, 4 postcards; dated 1995-1998. (Box 3, Folder 194)
    - MC GEE, LYNN. 2 letters; dated 1997-1998. (Box 3, Folder 195)
    - MALANGA, GERARD. 2 letters, 2 postcards; dated 1981; plus 7 pages of poetry. (Box 3, Folder 196)
    - MARGOLIN, MALCOLM. 1 letter; dated 1998. (Box 3, Folder 197)
    - MARRANCA, RICHARD. 5 letters; dated 1996-1998. (Box 3, Folder 198)
    - MARSHALL, BERTIE. 5 letters, 1 postcard; dated 1995-1996. (Box 3, Folder 199)
    - MASTERS, GREG. 1 letter; dated 1982. (Box 3, Folder 200)
    - MEADOWS, DEBORAH. 10 letters; dated 1988-1993. (Box 3, Folder 201)
    - MELILLO, MARCIE. 3 letters, 8 faxes, 5 emails, 3 cards; dated 1996-1997. (Box 3, Folder 202)
    - MERRITT, JAMES. 3 letters; dated 1989-1990. (Box 3, Folder 203)
    - MOHR, BILL. 1 letter; dated 1992. (Box 3, Folder 204)
    - MONEY, PETER. 2 pages of poetry; dated 1989. (Box 3, Folder 205)
    - MONTE, BRYAN R. 4 letters, 3 postcards; dated 1985-1988. (Box 3, Folder 206)
    - MORGAN, BRYAN. 1 letter; dated 1992. (Box 3, Folder 207)
    - MORRISON, RICHARD. 1 letter; dated 1995. (Box 3, Folder 208)
    - MOSS, HOWARD. 2 letters; dated 1986. (Box 3, Folder 209)
    - MULLINS, BRIGHDE. 1 letter; dated 1991. (Box 3, Folder 210)
    - MUNRO, LYN. 2 letters, 1 postcard; dated 1972-1997. (Box 3, Folder 211)
    - MURRAY, CHRISTOPHER. 4 letters; dated 1995-1997; plus chapbook. (Box 3, Folder 212)
    - MUSKE, CAROL. 1 postcard, 2 emails; dated 1998. (Box 3, Folder 213)
    - MYCUE, ED. 1 letter; dated 1985. (Box 3, Folder 214)
    - NETTELS, GAIL R. 9 letters, 29 postcards, 6 cards, 1 email; dated 1981-1998. (Box 3, Folder 215)
    - NIN, ANAIS. 1 postcard; dated 1973. (Box 3, Folder 216)
    - NORTH, CHARLES. 1 letter; dated 1989. (Box 3, Folder 217)
    - NORTHUP, HARRY. 5 letters; dated 1986-1988; plus one page of poetry. (Box 3, Folder 218)
    - NOTLEY, ALICE. 6 letters, 2 postcards, 2 emails; ca. 1982-1998; plus 12 pages of poetry; handwritten copy of "Song"; inscribed copy of Sorrento; Alternative Press postcard; etc. (Box 3, Folder 219)
    - OLIVEIRA, DAVID. 1 letter; dated 1994. (Box 3, Folder 220)
    - OLIVER, MARY. 1 letter; dated 1998. (Box 3, Folder 221)
    - OSTRIKER, ALICIA. 2 letters; dated 1996-1998. (Box 3, Folder 222)
    - O'SULLIVAN, WYLIE. 1 letter, 1 fax; dated 1998. (Box 3, Folder 223)
    - PEABODY, RICHARD. 2 letters, 1 postcard; dated 1992-1994. (Box 3, Folder 224)
    - PEACOCK, MOLLY. 4 letters, 1 card; dated 1993-1998. (Box 3, Folder 225)
    - PEARLBERG, GERRY GOMEZ. 3 letters, 4 postcards, 1 card, 1 fax, 8 emails; dated 1996-1998. (Box 4, Folder 226)
    - PEARSON, MARLENE. 4 letters, 1 postcard; dated 1992-1997. (Box 4, Folder 227)
    - PECK, CLAUDE. 10 letters, 5 postcards; dated 1986-1992; plus 4 pages of poetry; and 4 photographs of DT in Minneapolis in 1989. (Box 4, Folder 228)
    - PEYSER, CAROLYN. 1 letter; dated 1992. (Box 4, Folder 229)
    - PHILLIPS, CARL. 2 letters; dated 1997-1998. (Box 4, Folder 230)
    - POETS & WRITERS. 1 letter; dated 1981. (Box 4, Folder 231)
    - POKORNA, TEREZIE (Revolver Revue). 1 letter; dated 1993. (Box 4, Folder 232)
    - POLITO, ROBERT. 1 card; dated 1998. (Box 4, Folder 233)
    - POWELL, DOUGLAS. 1 letter, 6 emails; dated 1997-1998. (Box 4, Folder 234)
    - PRADEL, KARL A. 10 letters, 11 postcards, 2 cards; dated 1993-1998; plus 3 pages of poetry; and 7-page school paper on Dennis Cooper's Frisk. (Box 4, Folder 235)
    - PRADO, HOLLY. 1 letter, 1 postcard; dated 1981. (Box 4, Folder 236)
    - PRICE, CLARISE (co-worker at L.A. Housing Authority). 1 letter; dated 1986. (Box 4, Folder 237)
    - PUGSLEY, ALEX. 7 letters, 1 postcard; dated 1994-1998; plus 1 letter from Laura MacDonald. (Box 4, Folder 238)
    - PULLINGER, KATE. 4 letters, 2 postcards; dated 1994-1998. (Box 4, Folder 239)
    - QUINN, ALICE. 2 letters; dated 1992-1998. (Box 4, Folder 240)
    - RABINOWITZ, ANNA. 2 letters; dated 1997-1998. (Box 4, Folder 241)
    - RACKIN, ETHEL. 3 letters, 1 postcard; dated 1998. (Box 4, Folder 242)
    - RADKO, THOMAS R. 1 letter, 3 emails; dated 1998. (Box 4, Folder 243)
    - REED, REX. 1 letter; dated 1997. (Box 4, Folder 244)
    - REIDHEAD, JULIA A. 3 letters; dated 1993-1998. (Box 4, Folder 245)
    - REX, MONICA. 2 letters; dated 1985. (Box 4, Folder 246)
    - RHODES, MARTHA. 1 fax; dated 1998. (Box 4, Folder 247)
    - RICH, ADRIENNE. 2 letters, 1 postcard; dated 1992-1998. (Box 4, Folder 248)
    - RODRIGUEZ-GAONA, MARTIN. 2-page response to Hand Over Heart; ca. 1995; plus inscribed copy of Efectos Personales. (Box 4, Folder 249)
    - ROSENFIELD, KIM. 2 letters; dated 1985. (Box 4, Folder 250)
    - ROSENSTOCK, HELEN. 1 letter, 2 postcards, 1 card; dated 1988-1995; plus various notes and heath information. (Box 4, Folder 251)
    - ROWER, ANN. 1 letter; dated 1993. (Box 4, Folder 252)
    - RUDMAN, MARK. 1 letter; ca. 1989 (Box 4, Folder 253)
    - SAINT, ASSOTTO. 1 letter; dated 1990. (Box 4, Folder 254)
    - SALA, JEROME. 1 letter; dated 1985. (Box 4, Folder 255)
    - SAPPHIRE. 2 letters; dated 1992-1996. (Box 4, Folder 256)
    - SCALERA, HOLLY. 4 letters, 1 postcard, 4 cards; dated 1991-1997; plus 6 pages of poetry. (Box 4, Folder 257)
    - SCATES, MAXINE. 2 letters, 1 fax, 36 emails; dated 1997-1998; plus 6-page Xerox of essay on Ann Stanford's poetry and 2 pages of poetry. (Box 4, Folder 258)
    - SCHIMEL, LAWRENCE. 3 letters; dated 1994-1995. (Box 4, Folder 259)
    - SCHMIDT, PAUL. 6 letters, 1 postcard; dated 1985-1986. (Box 4, Folder 260)
    - SCHNEIDRE, PETER. 13 letters, 4 postcards; dated 1984-1990; plus corrected galleys of Living Doll chapbook; fliers; etc. (Box 4, Folder 261)
    - SCHOLDER, AMY. 2 letters, 4 postcards, 1 fax; dated 1990-1998. (Box 4, Folder 262)
    - SCHULZ, HART. 6 letters, 1 postcard; ca. 1984-1985; plus 5 pages of poetry. (Box 4, Folder 263)
    - SCHUMAN, MEREDITH. 8 letters, 1 postcard, 1 card; dated 1994-1998; plus 2 pages of poetry. (Box 4, Folder 264)
    - SCHUYLER, JAMES. 29 letters, 15 postcards, 1 card; dated 1985-1990; plus 13 pages of poetry; handwritten copy of "A Cardinal"; inscribed "Shaker" broadside; inscribed copies of May 24 or So, A Sun Cab, Early in '71, For Joe Brainard, and Collabs; copy of JS's last manuscript; miscellaneous items sent with letters; tear sheets; etc. (Box 4, Folder 265)
    - SCHUYLER, JAMES. cont'd, undated (Box 4, Folder 266)
    - SCHUYLER, JAMES. cont'd, undated (Box 4, Folder 267)
    - SCHUYLER, JAMES. cont'd, undated (Box 4, Folder 268)
    - SCHWARTZ, LLOYD. 1 letter; dated 1995. (Box 4, Folder 269)
    - SEAMAN, BARBARA. 1 postcard; dated 1997. (Box 4, Folder 270)
    - SEDEY, ALLISON (Lyn Munro's daughter). 6 letters; dated 1986-1998. (Box 4, Folder 271)
    - SELMAN, ROBYN. 17 letters, 21 postcards; dated 1991-1998; plus 9 pages of poetry. (Box 4, Folder 272)
    - SESHADRI, VIJAY. 2 letters; dated 1998. (Box 4, Folder 273)
    - SHALFOROOSH, SORAYA. 2 letters, 1 postcard; dated 1998. (Box 4, Folder 274)
    - SHARPE, MARTHA. 1 letter; dated 1998; plus galleys of Lynn Crosbie's Queen Rat. (Box 4, Folder 275)
    - SHEAR, JACK. 1 letter; dated 1985. (Box 4, Folder 276)
    - SHECK, LAURIE. 1 note; ca. 1996 (Box 4, Folder 277)
    - SHEEDY, CHARLOTTE. 2 letters; dated 1998. (Box 4, Folder 278)
    - SHERWOOD, RACHEL. 4 letters, 7 cards; ca. 1978-1979; plus obituaries of RS; correspondence regarding RS's poems; blue folder with RS's poems and worksheets, fliers of readings, reviews of Mysteries of Afternoon and Evening, etc.; tearsheets of Gerard Malanga poem about photograph of RS; copy of Foreign Exchange with poem by RS; etc. (Box 4, Folder 279)
    - SHERWOOD, RACHEL. cont'd, undated (Box 4, Folder 280)
    - SILVERBERG, FRAN (Ira Silverberg's sister). 1 letter, 1 postcard; dated 1994-1995. (Box 4, Folder 281)
    - SILVERBERG, IRA. 2 letters, 14 postcards; dated 1989-1998; plus numerous notes, cards, announcements, mementos of trips, etc. (Box 4, Folder 282)
    - SILVERBERG, IRA. cont'd, undated (Box 4, Folder 283)
    - SILVERNAIL, DANIEL (Jean Devereaux's son). 3 letters, 1 postcard; dated 989-1990. (Box 4, Folder 284)
    - SIMIC, CHARLES. 2 letters, 1 postcard; dated 1996-1997. (Box 4, Folder 285)
    - SKELLEY, JACK. 15 letters, 3 postcards, 1 card; dated 1981-1998; plus 9 pages of poetry; handwritten copy of "Disneyland"; inscribed copies of 9 chapbooks and pamphlets [some removed to Downtown]; various fliers; etc. (Box 4, Folder 286)
    - SMITH, DAVID. 1 letter; dated 1982. (Box 4, Folder 287)
    - SMITH, ED. 1 letter; ca. 1988; plus 9 pages of poetry. (Box 4, Folder 288)
    - SMITH, GEORGE DRURY. 1 letter; dated 1997. (Box 4, Folder 289)
    - SMITH, JOAN JOBE. 10 letters; dated 1991-1998. (Box 4, Folder 290)
    - SMITH, PATTI. 3 letters, 1 card; dated 1992-1993. (Box 4, Folder 291)
    - SMITH, ROY. 5 letters, 1 postcard, 3 cards; dated 1984-1991. (Box 4, Folder 292)
    - SHARON (married name: Jansen). 1 letter, 20 emails; dated 1979-1998; plus 12 pages of poetry. (Box 4, Folder 293)
    - CHUCK. 2 letters, 1 postcard; ca. 1991-1995; plus 2 pages of poetry. (Box 4, Folder 294)
    - SOFRON, DEMOSTENE. 5 letters; dated 1992-1996; plus Romanian publications with translations of DT's poems. (Box 5, Folder 295)
    - SOMERVILLE, SIOBHAN. 1 postcard; dated 1991. (Box 5, Folder 296)
    - SONSINI, JOHN. 1 letter; dated 1984. (Box 5, Folder 297)
    - SPIEGEL, JUDITH. 1 postcard; dated 1988. (Box 5, Folder 298)
    - STAMBOLIAN, GEORGE. 2 letters; dated 1987. (Box 5, Folder 299)